Guide to the Leverich Family Papers 1817-1937 (Bulk 1820-1890) MS 381
New-York Historical Society
- Series II. Business/Financial Papers, 1818, 1825-1890
  Leverich & Co. went into liquidation in 1879. The bulk of the material from 1880 to 1890 concerns the management of the Oak Lawn and Dogberry Plantations in Bayou Teche, Louisiana. The plantations had been owned by James Porter, for whom Leverich & Co. had acted as factors. By 1873, Leverich & Co. held the mortgages to both plantations, and in 1881 Edward Leverich and his wife Annie purchased them outright. The main crop of Oak Lawn and Dogberry was sugar, and much of the material involves its cultivation and processing. Other items record the workings and expenses of the plantation store, and purchases by and sales to tenants. Of particular note are the payrolls of the plantations, which record a large contingent of Chinese laborers in the plantations' workforce (see Subseries 2, Box 33, Folder 4). The last dated folder in the series contains material from 1890.
  - Subseries 1: Account Books, 1818, 1827-1890
    Includes journals, ledgers, daybooks, waste books, cash books, sales books, receipt books, record books, invoice books, memorandum books, storage books, cartage books, cotton broker books, and inventories. The account books span 1818, 1827-1890. Where an account book has an actual title, that title appears in quotes (e.g. Leverich & Co.: "Book of Charges"). The volumes in this subseries deal with both business and household expenses. They range from large journals and ledgers encompassing multiple years to small memorandum books and account books recording such transactions as weights of sugar cane or accounts with a butcher. Volumes exist for Leverich & Co., Henry S. Leverich, Charles P. Leverich, Edward Leverich, and Annie Leverich. A few account books and memorandum books also exist for the following people: George Payne, Margaret Leverich, and William H. Leverich; and William U. Persiani, and J.D. Fowler, presumably colleagues of the Leveriches. Checkbooks and bank books are located under the Checks, Notes, Exchanges subseries. Records books dealing with insurance companies are located in Series III. Legal, Taxes, Insurance.
    Listed alphabetically by creator. Chronological list also available at repository.
    - [J.D. Fowler]: "J.D. Fowler in Act. with H.S. & C.P. Leverich", 1856-1859 (Offsite-box 55)
    - [Annie Leverich]: Memorandum Book, 1887 (Offsite-box 55)
    - [Annie Leverich]: Notes Due - 1887 (Offsite-box 55)
    - Annie Leverich: Mrs. A. F. L., 1888-1890 (Offsite-box 55)
    - [Annie Leverich/Edward Leverich]: Portions of Memo / Note Books, [1880-1890] (Offsite-box 55)
    - Charles P. Leverich: [Receipt Book], 1835-1855 (Offsite-box 54)
    - [Charles P. Leverich]: "H. S. L. to C. P. L. 1 Jany. to 1 July 1838" (Offsite-box 56)
    - [Charles P. Leverich]: "H. S. L. to C. P. L. 1st. July to 31st. Decemr. 1838" (Offsite-box 56)
    - [Charles P. Leverich]: "H. S. L. _ to C.[P. L.] Jany. 1. 1839 to [Mar. 1840]", 1839-1840 (Offsite-box 56)
    - [Charles P. Leverich]: "H. S. L. to C. P. L. Dr. 1st. April 1840 to", 1840-1842 (Offsite-box 56)
    - [Charles P. Leverich]: Day Book, 1841-1846 (Offsite-box 67, Volume 34)
    - Charles P. Leverich: J. Moore Weighing -- C. P. Leverich, 1846-1855 (Offsite-box 55)
    - Charles P. Leverich: "Day Book No. 3", 1849-1854 (Offsite-box 67, Volume 35)
    - [Charles P. Leverich]: "Consignments", undated (Offsite-box 56)
    - [Charles P. Leverich]: "Consignments", undated (Offsite-box 56)
    - Edward Leverich: Day Book, 1863-1864 (Offsite-box 56)
    - [Edward Leverich]: "Ledger", 1881-1883 (Offsite-box 72, Volume 61)
    - [Edward Leverich]: "Daybook", 1881 (Offsite-box 72, Volume 62)
    - [Edward Leverich]: [Receipt Book for Syrup], 1885-1886 (Offsite-box 54)
    - [Edward Leverich]: "Weight of Cane for Acc't J. J. Michael 1887 Oak Lawn Plantation", 1886-1887 (Offsite-box 55)
    - [Edward Leverich]: "Weight of Cane for Acct Luke Roman. 1887 Oak Lawn Plantation", 1886-1887 (Offsite-box 55)
    - [Edward Leverich]: "Inventory of Contents of Overseer's House Mr. Stirling", undated (Offsite-box 55)
    - [Edward Leverich]: "Inventory of Furniture in House No. 28 East 30th Street belonging to Edwd. Leverich", undated (Offsite-box 55)
    - [Edward Leverich]: "Furniture - Inventory of House No. 28 East 30th Street belonging to Edwd. Leverich", undated (Offsite-box 55)
    - Henry S. Leverich: [Receipt Book], 1827-1828 (Offsite-box 54)
    - Henry S. Leverich: Ledger, 1827-1841 (Offsite-box 65, Volume 25)
    - Henry S. Leverich: Journal, 1827-1831 (Offsite-box 65, Volume 26)
    - Henry S. Leverich: Cash Book, 1827-1832 (Offsite-box 65, Volume 27)
    - Henry S. Leverich: [Receipt Book], 1828-1829 (Offsite-box 54)
    - Henry S. Leverich: [Receipt Book], 1829-1830 (Offsite-box 54)
    - Henry S. Leverich: [Receipt Book], 1830-1831 (Offsite-box 54)
    - Henry S. Leverich: [Receipt Book], 1831 (Offsite-box 54)
    - Henry S. Leverich: [Receipt Book], 1835-1841 (Offsite-box 54)
    - Henry S. Leverich: "Sales Book", 1835-1850 (Offsite-box 66, Volume 30)
    - Henry S. Leverich: "Journal C", 1838-1846 (Offsite-box 66, Volume 31)
    - Henry S. Leverich: Cash Book, 1841-1846 (Offsite-box 66, Volume 32)
    - Henry S. Leverich: Sales Journal, 1840-1846 (Offsite-box 67, Volume 33)
    - Henry S. Leverich: Mr. H. S. Leverich in account with [Mrs. S. A. Howard] (Household), 1883-1884 (Offsite-box 56)
    - Henry S. Leverich: Mr. Henry S. Leverich...in Account with John A. Prigge... (Household), 1880-1881 (Offsite-box 56)
    - Henry S. Leverich: Mr. H. S. Leverich in Account with Clement & Bloodgood... (Household), 1873-1876 (Offsite-box 56)
    - Henry S. Leverich: H. S. Leverich in Account with Geo. [Pople]... (Household), 1875 (Offsite-box 56)
    - Henry S. Leverich: Henry S. Leverich in account with E. L. van Wickle (Household), 1879-1882 (Offsite-box 56)
    - Henry S. Leverich: Mr. Henry S. Leverich... in Account with John A. Prigge... (Household), 1880-1881 (Offsite-box 56)
    - [Henry S. Leverich]: Sales Book / Invoice Book, 1827-1830 (Offsite-box 65, Volume 28)
    - [Henry S. Leverich]: Sales Book / Invoice Book, 1830-1832 (Offsite-box 66, Volume 29)
    - [Henry S. Leverich]: [Account Book], 1835 July-November (Offsite-box 56)
    - Henry S. Leverich: [Account Book], 1833 October-1836 March (Offsite-box 56)
      Scope and Contents Note
      This account book was a gift of David Bosse, 2014.
    - [Henry S. Leverich]: "C. P. L. agst. H. S. L. Decemr. 1835 to April 1836", 1835-1836 (Offsite-box 56)
    - [Henry S. Leverich]: "Petty Cash C. P. L. agst. H. S. L. April to June 1836" (Offsite-box 56)
    - [Henry S. Leverich]: "C. P. L. agst. H. S. L. June to Sept 1836" (Offsite-box 56)
    - [Henry S. Leverich]: "C. P. Leverich a/c Septemr. 1836 to Jan. 1837", 1836-1837 (Offsite-box 56)
    - [Henry S. Leverich]: "C. P. L. agst. H. S. L. Jan. to April 1837" (Offsite-box 56)
    - [Henry S. Leverich]: "C. P. L. agst. H. S. L. April 1837 to July 1837" (Offsite-box 56)
    - [Henry S. Leverich]: "C. P. L. against H. S. L. July 1837 to 14 Nov. 1837" (Offsite-box 56)
    - [Henry S. Leverich]: "H. S. L. to C. P. L. Nov. to Jany. 1838", 1837-1838 (Offsite-box 56)
    - [Henry S. Leverich]: [Receipt Book], 1851-1852 (Offsite-box 54)
    - [Henry S. Leverich]: Household Account Book, 1872-1876 (Offsite-box 56)
    - [Henry S. Leverich]: Purchases and Sales, 1877-1878 (Offsite-box 55)
    - [Henry S. Leverich]: Mr. [Henry S.] Leverich in Account with John A. Prigge... (Household), 1879-1880 (Offsite-box 56)
    - [Henry S. Leverich]: Mr. H. Leverich in Account with William Riesz... (Household), 1882-1883 (Offsite-box 56)
    - [Henry S. Leverich]: Machinery Shipped for Mrs. Porter on Schooner 'Decatur Oakes', undated (Offsite-box 55)
    - [Henry S. Leverich]: Inventory Mrs. M. A. Gustine, undated (Offsite-box 55)
    - [Leverich & Co.]: "A. Baker's Cartage Book -- 1830" (Offsite-box 55)
    - Leverich & Co.: "Abrm. Baker's Cartage Book agst. Henry S. Leverich New York 1. May 1835", 1835-1838 (Offsite-box 55)
    - [Leverich & Co.]: "Book of Charges", 1837-1854 (Offsite-box 67, Volume 36)
    - Leverich & Co.: "Payable", "Receivable", 1839-1848 (Offsite-box 68, Volume 40)
    - Leverich & Co.: [Account Book], 1842, 1846-1868 (Offsite-box 55)
    - Leverich & Co.: "Cartage Book. Leverich & Co. with T. L. Asten.", 1860-1869 (Offsite-box 55)
    - Leverich & Co.: "Adams Express Company Money Receipts", 1863-1870 (Offsite-box 54)
    - Leverich & Co.: "Storage Book No. 1", 1865-1869 (Offsite-box 68, Volume 38)
    - Leverich & Co.: "Waste Book", 1865-1869 (Offsite-box 68, Volume 39)
    - Leverich & Co.: "Sales Book", 1865-1869 (Offsite-box 68, Volume 41)
    - Leverich & Co.: "Payable", "Receivable", 1865-1872 (Offsite-box 68, Volume 42)
    - [Leverich & Co.]: Gold Checks, 1867-1874 (Offsite-box 56)
    - Leverich & Co.: "Cartage Memo Book", 1868 (Offsite-box 69, Volume 43)
    - Leverich & Co.: "Leverich & Co. Cooperage Book", 1868-1870 (Offsite-box 55)
    - Leverich & Co.: "Money Receipts A. Ex. Co.", 1868-1870 (Offsite-box 54)
    - Leverich & Co.: "Check Book Bank of New-York No. 2", 1868-1871 (Offsite-box 69, Volume 44)
    - Leverich & Co.: "Leverich & Co. Receipts", 1868-1872 (Offsite-box 56)
    - Leverich & Co.: Ledger, 1868-1872 (Offsite-box 69, Volume 45)
    - Leverich & Co.: "Cotton", 1868-1873 (Offsite-box 70, Volume 50)
    - Leverich & Co.: "Cash No. 1", 1868-1874 (Offsite-box 69, Volume 46)
    - Leverich & Co.: "Rice Book No. 1", 1868-1876 (Offsite-box 69, Volume 47)
    - Leverich & Co.: Ledger, 1870-1874 (Offsite-box 56)
    - Leverich & Co.: "Cartage Book Leverich & Co. with T. L. Asten.", 1870-1876 (Offsite-box 55)
    - Leverich & Co.: "Money Receipts A. Ex. Co.", 1870-1876 (Offsite-box 54)
    - Leverich & Co.: Cash book "Top", 1871-1873 (Offsite-box 70, Volume 49)
    - Leverich & Co.: Cotton Brokering Book, 1873-1876 (Offsite-box 71, Volume 53)
    - Leverich & Co.: Cotton Brokering Book, 1874 (Offsite-box 71, Volume 54)
    - Leverich & Co.: Cotton Brokering Book, 1874 (Offsite-box 71, Volume 55)
    - Leverich & Co.: "Bill Collections Leverich & Co.", 1874-1875 (Offsite-box 55)
    - Leverich & Co.: "January--February--March.", 1875-1877 (Offsite-box 72, Volume 59)
    - Leverich & Co.: "April--May--June.", 1875-1877 (Offsite-box 72, Volume 56)
    - Leverich & Co.: "July--August--September.", 1875-1877 (Offsite-box 72, Volume 58)
    - Leverich & Co.: "October--November--December.", 1875-1877 (Offsite-box 72, Volume 57)
    - Leverich & Co.: ["Spots"], 1876-1877 (Offsite-box 70, Volume 51)
    - Leverich & Co.: "Spots", 1876-1878 (Offsite-box 70, Volume 52)
    - Leverich & Co.: Cotton Brokering Book, 1876-1878 (Offsite-box 71, Volume 60)
    - Leverich & Co.: "Peck & Walsh Mending a/c with Leverich & Co.", undated (Offsite-box 55)
    - [Leverich & Co.]: [Cotton Shipments], undated (Offsite-box 56)
    - [Leverich & Co.]: [Cotton Shipments], undated (Offsite-box 56)
    - [Leverich & Co.]: [Cotton Shipments], undated (Offsite-box 56)
    - [Leverich & Co.]: [Cotton Shipments], undated (Offsite-box 56)
    - [Leverich & Co.]: [Cotton Shipments], undated (Offsite-box 56)
    - [Leverich & Co.]: [Cotton Shipments], undated (Offsite-box 56)
    - [Leverich & Co.]: [Cotton Shipments], undated (Offsite-box 56)
    - [Leverich & Co.]: [Shipment Book], undated (Offsite-box 56)
    - [Margaret Leverich]: "Mrs. Leverich in Account with William Riesz..." (Household), 1879-1880 (Offsite-box 56)
    - Wm. H. Leverich: Memorandum Book, Consignments, 1818, 1846 (Offsite-box 56)
    - Wm. H. Leverich: Consignments, Memorandum Book, 1840, 1847 (Offsite-box 56)
    - Wm. H. Leverich: Memorandum Book, Consignments, 1847-1848 (Offsite-box 56)
    - [George Payne]: [Record of Weather], 1885-1887 (Offsite-box 55)
    - [George Payne]: "1887 Tests of Juice"; "Tests of Syrup" (Offsite-box 55)
    - Wm. U. Persiani: Consignments, 1850-1853 (Offsite-box 56)
    - Wm. U. Persiani: Day Book Memorandums, 1852-1853 (Offsite-box 56)
    - [Index to Unidentified Volumes], undated (Offsite-box 55)
  - Subseries 2: Bills, Receipts, Invoices, Transferable Orders for Cotton, Payrolls, Charges, 1825-1890
    Contains material that concerns the exchange of goods and services for cash or, more simply put, those transactions of more of a singular nature. The utility of integrating these forms in a single series is that the same document may at different times have served more than one function: an itemized list of goods may have, at the bottom of the sheet, a request for remittance, and below the request, written at a later date, the notation "Recd. Payment". Such an item would have been created as an invoice, submitted as a bill, and been returned to the debtor as a receipt after the creditor had received payment. This section includes bills, receipts (acknowledgments of payment), and invoices paid by Leverich & Co. in its own right as well as bills paid by the firm on behalf of its clients. It also includes household bills of the various Leverich households. Transferable Orders for Cotton are orders to one firm to deliver cotton at a given date at a given price. Charges are costs associated with specific shipments of goods.
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices: "Bills Settled to 1st Sept. 1828 -- Merchandize", 1827 Aug. - 1828 Aug. (Offsite-box 19, Folder 1)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices: "Bills Settled from 1st Setp. 1828 to 1st Sept. 1830 -- Merchandize", 1828 Sept. - 1828 Dec. (Offsite-box 19, Folder 2)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices: "Bills Settled from 1st Sept. 1828 to 1st Sept. 1830 -- Merchandize", 1829 Jan. - 1829 Sept. (Offsite-box 19, Folder 3)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices: "Bills Settled from Sept. 1, 1828 to Sept. 1, 1830 -- Merchandize", 1829 Oct. - 1829 Dec. (Offsite-box 19, Folder 4)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices: "Bills Settled from Sept. 1, 1828 to Sept. 1, 1830 -- Merchandize", 1830 Jan. - 1830 Nov. (Offsite-box 19, Folder 5)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices: "Invoices Inward to 1st January 1832", 1827 Oct. - 1831 Aug. (Offsite-box 19, Folder 6)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices: "Weigher's Returns. to 1st January 1832", 1827 Dec. - 1829 Dec. 1830 Apr. - 1832 Feb. (Offsite-box 19, Folder 7)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices: "Petty Bills Paid to January 1835", 1825 Oct. - 1829 Dec. (Offsite-box 19, Folder 8)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices: "Petty Bills -- Paid to January 1835", 1830 Jan. - 1831 Dec. (Offsite-box 20, Folder 1)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices: "Petty Bills Paid to January 1835", 1832 Jan. - 1834 Dec. (Offsite-box 20, Folder 2)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices: "Returns 1835 to 1839", 1835 Jan. - 1839 Jan. (Offsite-box 20, Folder 3)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices: "Private Bills Paid to 1st Jan. 1836", 1826 Feb. - 1832 Dec. (Offsite-box 20, Folder 4)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices: "Private Bills Paid to 1st Jan. 1836", 1835 Jan. - 1837 Jan. (Offsite-box 20, Folder 5)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices: "Petty Bills 1837 & 1838", 1837 Jan. - 1837 Dec. (Offsite-box 20, Folder 6)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices: "Petty Bills 1837 & 1838", 1838 Jan. - 1839 Jan. (Offsite-box 21, Folder 1)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices: "Bills Paid -- June 1837 to July 1838 -- Merchandize", 1838 Mar. - 1838 Sept. (Offsite-box 21, Folder 2)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices: "Private Bills Paid 1837 to 1838", 1837 Dec. - 1838 Dec. (Offsite-box 21, Folder 3)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices: "Orders. 1838" (Offsite-box 21, Folder 4)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices: "Bills Paid -- July to January 1838 - 1839", 1838 Jun. - 1838 Sept. (Offsite-box 21, Folder 5)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices: "Bills Paid -- July to January 1838 - 1839", 1838 Oct. - 1839 Jan. (Offsite-box 21, Folder 6)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, 1826-1829 (Offsite-box 22, Folder 1)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, 1830 (Offsite-box 22, Folder 2)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, 1831 Jan. - 1831 May (Offsite-box 22, Folder 3)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, 1831 Jun. - 1831 Dec. (Offsite-box 22, Folder 4)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, 1832, 1835 (Offsite-box 22, Folder 5)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, 1836 (Offsite-box 22, Folder 6)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, 1837 Jan. - 1837 Sept. (Offsite-box 22, Folder 7)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, 1837 Oct. - 1837 Dec. (Offsite-box 23, Folder 1)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, 1838 (Offsite-box 23, Folder 2)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, 1840-1846 (Offsite-box 23, Folder 3)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, 1847-1848 (Offsite-box 23, Folder 4)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, 1849 (Offsite-box 23, Folder 5)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, [1840-1850] (Offsite-box 23, Folder 6)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, 1850-1851 (Offsite-box 23, Folder 7)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, 1852 (Offsite-box 23, Folder 8)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, 1853-1854 (Offsite-box 24, Folder 1)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, 1855 (Offsite-box 24, Folder 2)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, 1856 (Offsite-box 24, Folder 3)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, 1857 (Offsite-box 24, Folder 4)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, 1858 Jan. - 1858 Sept. (Offsite-box 24, Folder 5)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, 1858 Oct. - 1858 Dec. (Offsite-box 24, Folder 6)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, 1859 Jan. - 1859 Mar. (Offsite-box 25, Folder 1)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, 1859 Apr. - 1859 Sept. (Offsite-box 25, Folder 2)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, 1859 Oct. - 1859 Dec. (Offsite-box 25, Folder 3)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, [1850-1860] (Offsite-box 25, Folder 4)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, 1860 Jan. - 1860 Mar. (Offsite-box 25, Folder 5)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, 1860 Apr. - 1860 Sept. (Offsite-box 25, Folder 6)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, 1860 Oct. - 1860 Dec. (Offsite-box 25, Folder 7)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, 1861 (Offsite-box 26, Folder 1)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, 1862 (Offsite-box 26, Folder 2)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, 1863 Jan. - 1863 May (Offsite-box 26, Folder 3)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, 1863 Jun. - 1863 Dec. (Offsite-box 26, Folder 4)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, 1864 (Offsite-box 26, Folder 5)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, 1865 (Offsite-box 26, Folder 6)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, 1866 Jan. - 1866 Mar. (Offsite-box 26, Folder 7)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, 1866 Apr. - 1866 Jun. (Offsite-box 26, Folder 8)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, 1866 Jul.- 1866 Sept. (Offsite-box 27, Folder 1)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, 1866 Oct. - 1866 Dec. (Offsite-box 27, Folder 2)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, 1867 Jan. - 1867 Mar. (Offsite-box 27, Folder 3)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, 1867 Apr. - 1867 Aug. (Offsite-box 27, Folder 4)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, 1867 Sept. - 1867 Dec. (Offsite-box 27, Folder 5)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, 1868 Jan. - 1868 Mar. (Offsite-box 27, Folder 6)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, 1868 Apr. - 1868 Sept. (Offsite-box 28, Folder 1)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, 1868 Oct. - 1868 Dec. (Offsite-box 28, Folder 2)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, 1869 (Offsite-box 28, Folder 3)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, [1860-1870] (Offsite-box 28, Folder 4)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, 1870 Jan. - 1870 Apr. (Offsite-box 28, Folder 5)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, 1870 May - 1870 Aug. (Offsite-box 28, Folder 6)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, 1870 Sept. (Offsite-box 29, Folder 1)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, 1870 Oct. (Offsite-box 29, Folder 2)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, 1870 Nov. (Offsite-box 29, Folder 3)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, 1870 Nov. (Offsite-box 29, Folder 4)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, 1870 Dec. (Offsite-box 29, Folder 5)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, 1871 Jan. - 1871 Mar. (Offsite-box 29, Folder 6)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, 1871 Apr. - 1871 Jun. (Offsite-box 30, Folder 1)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, 1871 Jul. (Offsite-box 30, Folder 2)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, 1871 Aug. (Offsite-box 30, Folder 3)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, 1871 Sept. - 1871 Oct. (Offsite-box 30, Folder 4)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, 1871 Nov. - 1871 Dec. (Offsite-box 30, Folder 5)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, 1872 Jan. - 1872 Mar. (Offsite-box 30, Folder 6)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, 1872 Apr. - 1872 Jun. (Offsite-box 31, Folder 1)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, 1872 Jul. - 1872 Sept. (Offsite-box 31, Folder 2)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, 1872 Oct. - 1872 Dec. (Offsite-box 31, Folder 3)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, 1873 Jan. - 1873 Feb. (Offsite-box 31, Folder 4)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, 1873 Mar. (Offsite-box 31, Folder 5)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, 1873 Mar. (Offsite-box 32, Folder 1)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, 1873 Apr. (Offsite-box 32, Folder 2)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, 1873 May (Offsite-box 32, Folder 3)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, 1873 Jun. (Offsite-box 32, Folder 4)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, 1873 Jul. (Offsite-box 32, Folder 5)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, 1873 Jul. (Offsite-box 32, Folder 6)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, 1873 Jul. (Offsite-box 32, Folder 7)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, 1873 Aug. (Offsite-box 33, Folder 1)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, 1873 Aug. (Offsite-box 33, Folder 2)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, 1873 Aug. (Offsite-box 33, Folder 3)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, 1873 Aug. (Offsite-box 33, Folder 4)
      Scope and Contents
      Includes payroll for Chinese laborers, July 1873 (certified August 1873).
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, 1873 Sept. (Offsite-box 33, Folder 5)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, 1873 Oct. (Offsite-box 33, Folder 6)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, 1873 Nov. - 1873 Dec. (Offsite-box 33, Folder 7)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, 1874 Jan. - 1874 Apr. (Offsite-box 34, Folder 1)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, 1874 May - 1874 Jun. (Offsite-box 34, Folder 2)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, 1874 Jul. - 1874 Oct. (Offsite-box 34, Folder 3)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, 1874 Nov. - 1874 Dec. (Offsite-box 34, Folder 4)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, 1875 Jan. - 1875 Jun. (Offsite-box 34, Folder 5)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, 1875 Jul. - 1875 Oct. (Offsite-box 34, Folder 6)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, 1875 Nov. - 1875 Dec. (Offsite-box 34, Folder 7)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, 1876 Jan. (Offsite-box 35, Folder 1)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, 1876 Feb. - 1876 Mar. (Offsite-box 35, Folder 2)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, 1876 Apr. - 1876 Jun. (Offsite-box 35, Folder 3)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, 1876 Jul. - 1876 Sept. (Offsite-box 35, Folder 4)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, 1876 Oct. (Offsite-box 35, Folder 5)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, 1876 Nov. (Offsite-box 35, Folder 6)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, 1876 Dec. (Offsite-box 35, Folder 7)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, 1877 Jan. (Offsite-box 36, Folder 1)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, 1877 Feb. (Offsite-box 36, Folder 2)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, 1877 Mar. - 1877 Apr. (Offsite-box 36, Folder 3)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, 1877 May (Offsite-box 36, Folder 4)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, 1877 Jun. - 1877 Sept. (Offsite-box 36, Folder 5)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, 1877 Oct. - 1877 Dec. (Offsite-box 36, Folder 6)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, 1878-1879 (Offsite-box 37, Folder 1)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, [1870-1880] (Offsite-box 37, Folder 2)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, 1880-1884 (Offsite-box 37, Folder 3)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, 1886 (Offsite-box 37, Folder 4)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, 1887 Jan. - 1887 Jun. (Offsite-box 37, Folder 5)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, 1887 Jul. - 1887 Dec. (Offsite-box 37, Folder 6)
    - Bills, Receipts, Invoices, 1888 (Offsite-box 37, Folder 7)